RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 3. Subject Files, 1960-1971
  - Teachers, 1967; 5 folders (Box A-300)
  - Teachers, Conn. State Federation of - vs. Conn. Education Association, 1964 (Box A-300)
  - Teachers of English, 1961-1962, 1965-1965, 1969-1970 (Box A-300)
  - Teamsters' Strike, 1967 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Alcoholic Use Study Commission, 1966 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Drinking (10 folders, alphabetical), 1957-1967 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Drinking, 1955, 1960-1967, 1969 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Drinking - Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Drinking - Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1962 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Drinking Problem - Interdepartmental Coordinating Committee, 1964 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Drivers, 1962, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box A-301)
  - Teenage Liquor Law Coordination, 1963-1965, 1969 (Box A-301)
  - Television Service Examiners, 1967 (Box A-302)
  - Television Stations, 1962 (Box A-302)
  - Ten Outstanding Young Men re: 1959 Banquet, Hartford, Conn., 1958, 1962-1968 (Box A-302)
  - Testos, Robert J. (Speaker of the House), 1967-1968 (Box A-302)
  - Thames River Bridge in Norwich, Commission to Investigate and Report on a Proposed, 1959, 1965 (Box A-302)
  - Thames River Compact Basin, 1956-1957, 1959, 1964, 1967 (Box A-302)
  - Thames Valley Council for Community Action, Norwich, Conn., 1966-1970 (Box A-302)
  - Thanks for Troops, 1970 (Box A-302)
  - Thomaston Dam, 1957-1958 (Box A-302)
  - Tire Dealers, 1963-1964, 1967-1969 (Box A-302)
  - Toxicological Laboratory (State Health Dept.), 1961 (Box A-302)
  - Traffic Safety, Governor's Conference on, 1962-1964, 1966 (Box A-302)
  - Traffic Safety Stamp, 1964 (Box A-302)
  - Trahan, Michael, re: Pending Eviction from Home, 1964 (Box A-302)
  - Transportation Dept., 1968-1970 (Box A-302)
  - Transportation Dept., 1968-1970 (Box A-303)
  - Tristate Project - Regional Health Resources and Services, 1967 (Box A-303)
  - Tristate Transportation Commission, 1962, 1966-1968 (Box A-303)
  - Trucking Industry, re: Freight Rate Increase, 1962 (Box A-303)
  - Trumbull Airport, 1967 (Box A-303)
  - Trumbull-Bridgeport Line (Route 25), 1962 (Box A-303)
  - Tuberculosis, 1954-1957, 1964 (Box A-303)
  - Tugboat Operators Strike, 1961-1962 (Box A-303)
  - Tuition Fees, 1957-1958, 1961-1963, 1969-1970 (Box A-303)
  - Tunick House, 1969-1970 (Box A-303)
  - Uncommitted Children, 1962 (Box A-303)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1962 (Box A-303)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1958-1959, 1961, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box A-303)
  - Unemployment - Special Session, 1958 (Box A-303)
  - Unfair Sales Practices, 1963 (Box A-304)
  - Uninsured Motor Vehicles, Commission to Study the Problem, 1959-1960 (Box A-304)
  - Unmarked State Police Cars, 1962, 1965 (Box A-304)
  - Unsecured Loans, 1963 (Box A-304)
  - United Aircraft Corporation: Proposal for High Performance Inter-Urban Transportation System, 1964 (Box A-304)
  - United Parcel Service, 1965 (Box A-304)
  - U.S. Property and Fiscal Officer for Connecticut, 1956, 1962-1963 (Box A-304)
  - Urban Affairs and Housing, Dept. of, 1962, 1970-1971 (Box A-304)
  - Urban Renewal, 1961-1967, 1969 (Box A-304)
  - Urban School Needs (Study), 1968 (Box A-304)
  - Used Car Dealers, 1963-1964 (Box A-304)
  - U.S.S. Connecticut (Bill), 1966, 1969 (Box A-304)
  - Utility Company Taxes, 1961-1962 (Box A-304)
  - Vacation Travel Advisory Council, 1956-1957, 1968-1970 (Box A-304)
  - Vermin Control Committee, 1967-1970 (Box A-304)
  - Veterans Cemetery, 1969 (Box A-305)
  - Veterans Discharged, Lists of, 1968-1970; 12 inches (Box A-305)
  - Veterans' Preference, Hartford, 1963 (Box A-306)
  - Veterinary Medicine - UCONN, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box A-306)
  - Vietnam Bonus, 1967-1970 (Box A-306)
  - Vietnam Casualties, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box A-306)
  - Vietnam Correspondence, 1966, 1968-1970; 3 folders (Box A-306)
  - Vietnam Correspondence, 1966-1970; 4 folders (Box A-307)
  - Vietnam Moratorium, 1969 (Box A-307)
  - Vietnam Protest Letters, 1967-1969 (Box A-307)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, Advisory Council on, 1968-1969 (Box A-307)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation Division within State Dept. of Education, 1965 (Box A-307)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation Services (State Planning Council), 1968-1970 (Box A-307)
  - Vocational-Technical School (Stratford-Milford-West Haven area), 1965 (Box A-307)
  - Voting Age, 1967-1970 (Box A-307)
  - Voting Age, 1957, 1961-1962, 1966-1967 (Box A-308)
  - Walker Trucking Co. (Atomic Waste), 1958, 1961, 1964, 1966 (Box A-308)
  - Wallingford - Route 91, 1961-1963 (Box A-308)
  - Water Company's Report by Public Utilities Commission, 1966 July 14 (Box A-308)
  - Water Pollution, 1963-1964, 1968 (Box A-308)
  - Water Shortage, 1966 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Community College, 1967 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Hospital Strike, 1964 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Inter-Urban league, 1964 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Now Program, 1969 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Parkland Acres, 1968 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Property Tax, 1968 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Revaluation, 1965 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Taxes, 1968 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Teachers' Association, 1969 (Box A-308)
  - Waterbury Welfare March, 1968 (Box A-308)
  - Watertown, 1967 (Box A-308)
  - Welcome to Connecticut, 1964, 1968 (Box A-308)
  - Welfare Medical Fees, 1970 (Box A-308)
  - West Hartford Flooding, 1970 (Box A-308)
  - West Hartford - Interstate 291, 1969-1970 (Box A-308)
  - West Hartford - Interstate 291, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box A-309)
  - Western Conn. State College, 1969-1970 (Box A-309)
  - Westport Nike Site, 1964 (Box A-309)
  - Wethersfield - State Prison Site, 1967-1968 (Box A-309)
  - Wethersfield Testing Installation, 1970 (Box A-309)
  - Wet Lands - S.S.B. 491, 1969-1970 (Box A-309)
  - Wet Lands - S.B. 1819, 1968-1970 (Box A-309)
  - White House Conference on Children, 1960-1970, 1960, 1968-1969 (Box A-309)
  - White House Conference on Children, 1970, 1969-1970 (Box A-309)
  - White House Conference on Children, 1970 - Delegates (Box A-309)
  - White House Conference on Children, 1970 - Planning Committee (Box A-309)
  - White House Fellows, 1965, 1967-1970 (Box A-310)
  - White House Meeting, 1967 (Box A-310)
  - Whittelsay, Souther, 99 Old Church Road, Greenwich, Conn., 1956, 1958-1968 (Box A-310)
  - Wild Rice Management Institute Wildlife, 1970 (Box A-310)
  - Willimantic Court House, 1970 (Box A-310)
  - Willimantic River Pollution, 1964 (Box A-310)
  - Wire Tap Bill, 1969 (Box A-310)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1968, 1970 (Box A-310)
  - Wojculewicz, Frank (executed for killing two men; was paralyzed when executed), 1953, 1956-1959 (Box A-310)
  - Women at the Bar, 1967, 1969; 2 folders (Box A-310)
  - Women Inmates in State Jails, 1961 (Box A-310)
  - Women, Status of, Commission on the, 1962-1970; 2 folders (Box A-310)
  - Woodruff Hospital [1961] (Box A-311)
  - Work Training Program (Work Relief Program), 1961-1962 (Box A-311)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1967 (Box A-311)
  - Wozenski, Edward (Col.), 1961 (Box A-311)
  - Wrestling, 1961-1964 (Box A-311)
  - Atomic Power Plant, 1964 (Box A-311)
  - Yankee Atomic Power Co., 1964-1968; 10 inches (Box A-311)
  - Yankee Doodle Dandies Contest (Philadelphia Freedom Week Program), 1962 (Box A-311)
  - Young American; Medal for Bravery Award, 1951-1952, 1955-1970 (Box A-311)
  - Youth Authority, 1969 (Box A-312)
  - Youth Employment Act, 1963, 1966-1968 (Box A-312)
  - Youth Opportunity, Governor's Council on, 1966-1968, 1970 (Box A-312)
  - Youth Opportunity- Summer Camp (Filmstrip program called " There Comes A Day"), undated (Box A-312)
  - Youth Opportunity - Summer Employment, 1968-1970; 4 folders (Box A-312)
  - Youth Services, Commission on, 1962-1970; 4 folders + 2 binders (Box A-313)
  - Youthful Wards of the State, Committee to Study Custodial and Educational Programs for, 1966-1969 (Box A-313)
  - Yurewitch, John P. [1964-1965] (Box A-313)
  - Zoning, 1966-1967, 1969; 2 folders (Box A-313)
- Series 4. Agency Files, 1960-1971
  [Correspondence Files Boxes A-187 and A-188 contain unarranged Agency Files.]
  - Accountancy, Board of, 1963-1964 (Box A-314)
  - Adult Probation Department, 1961-1965, 1969 (Box A-314)
  - Aeronautics Department, 1961-1968; 2 folders (Box A-314)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1954-1970; 6 folders (Box A-314)
  - Agriculture and Natural Resources, 1967-1970 (Box A-315)
  - Agriculture Conservation and Natural Resources, Department of, 1962-1967, 1970 (Box A-315)
  - Alcoholism, Commission on, 1964-1967, 1970; 2 folders (Box A-315)
  - American School for the Deaf, 1964-1970 (Box A-315)
  - American School for the Deaf, 1961-1964, 1968-1970; 2 folders (Box A-316)
  - Annual Reports lists, 1963-1964 (Box A-316)
  - Annual Reports, 1967-1968; 10 inches (Box A-316)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1967; 12 inches (Box A-317)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1967; 2 inches (Box A-318)
  - Architectural Examining Board, 1964 (Box A-318)
  - Attorney General, 1961-1970; 2 folders (Box A-318)
  - Attorney General (Applications for), 1963, 1970 (Box A-318)
  - Attorney General Decisions [1935, 1941-1944, 1935, 1941-1944, 1946, 1948-1949, 1951, 1953, 1958-1959 (Box A-318)
  - Auditors of Public Accounts, 1961-1962, 1968-1970 (Box A-318)
  - Bank Commissioner, 1959-1961, 1963, 1967-1970 (Box A-318)
  - Bank Commissioner (Deputy), 1958-1959, 1961-1962 (Box A-318)
  - Bank Proclamations - Emergency Closings, 1960-1961, 1968-1969 (Box A-318)
  - Banking Department, 1960-1970; 2 folders (Box A-319)
  - Barbers, Board of Examiners of, 1962-1967 (Box A-319)
  - Blind, Board of Education of the, 1961-1966, 1969 (Box A-319)
  - Bond Commission, 1961-1969; 15 inches (Box A-320)
  - Bond Commission, 1956-1963; 12 inches (Box A-321)
  - Bond Commission, 1967-1970; 15 inches (Box A-322)
  - Bond Commission, 1969-1970; 8 inches (Box A-323)
  - Budget Division, 1961-1967, 1969, 1971; 2 folders (Box A-323)
  - Budget Report, 1961-1963 (Box A-323)
  - Budget - SA 386, 1961-1965 (Box A-324)
  - Budget, Tentative, 1965-1967 (Box A-324)
  - Chiropractic Examiners, Board of, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box A-324)
  - Civil Rights - King, Dr. Martin Luther, 1961-1965 (Box A-324)
  - Civil Rights Commission (6 folders) [1966, 1969; 1966-1967; 1966; 1963-1965, 1957-1967, 1969; 6 folders (Box A-324)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1957-1958, 1960-1962, 1965-1967 (Box A-324)
  - Claims Commission: (Public Act No. 685 - An Act Concerning the Hearing and Determination of Claims against the State), 1960-1961 (Box A-324)
  - Comptroller, Annual Reports of, 1961-1963, 1965, 1967, 1970 (Box A-325)
  - Comptroller, Department of, 1962-1966 (Box A-325)
  - Comptroller, Department of, Monthly Statements, 1960 December -1967 December (Box A-325)
  - Comptroller, Department of, Monthly Statements, 1968 January - 1970 October (Box A-326)
  - Connecticut Reformatory, 1959-1965 (Box A-326)
  - Connecticut Safety Commission, 1964-1969; 4 folders (Box A-326)
  - Connecticut Safety Commission, 1962-1964; 5 folders (Box A-327)
  - Connecticut Valley Hospital, 1964; 3 folders (Box A-327)
  - Consumer Protection, Department of, 1961-1963, 1965, 1967; 2 folders (Box A-328)
  - Dental Commission, 1964 (Box A-328)
  - Development Commission, 1963, 1965, 1967-1970; 10 inches (Box A-328)
  - Development Commission, 1961-1970; 12 inches (Box A-329)
  - Development Commission, 1963-1964; 2 folders (Box A-330)
  - Education, State Board of, 1963-1969; 8 inches (Box A-330)
  - Elderly Persons, Commission on Services for, 1964-1968 (Box A-330)
  - Elderly Citizens, Committee to Study Tax Burdens of, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1967 (Box A-331)
  - Embalmers and Funeral Directors, Board of, 1963-1964 (Box A-331)
  - Engineers and Land Surveyors, Board of Examiners for, 1961, 1963, 1965 (Box A-331)
  - Fairfield Hills Hospital, 1959, 1969 (Box A-331)
  - Fairfield State Hospital (Out-Patient Clinic, re: Drugs), 1957, 1961-1967 (Box A-331)
  - Finance Advisory Committee, 1955-1956, 1959, 1968; 6 inches (Box A-331)
  - Finance Advisory Committee, 1963-1970; 12 inches (Box A-332)
  - Finance Advisory Committee, 1958-1963; 8 inches (Box A-333)
  - Finance and Control, Department of, 1962-1966, 1969-1970; 4 inches (Box A-333)
  - Fish and Game (Complimentary Licenses), 1961-1964 (Box A-334)
  - Fisheries and Game, Board of, 1960-1970; 3 folders (Box A-334)
  - Forfeited Rights, Commission on, 1963-1964 (Box A-334)
  - Healing Arts, State Board of, 1961, 1964-1965 (Box A-334)
  - Health Department (4 folders) [1966-1970; 1964-1968; 1961-1964, 1968; 1961-1963], 1961-1970; 4 folders (Box A-334)
  - Health Department, 1965-1966, 1968-1969; 4 inches (Box A-335)
  - High Meadows (Child Study and Treatment Home), 1961-1964 (Box A-335)
  - Higher Education, Commission for, 1968-1969; 5 binders (Box A-335)
  - Higher Education, Commission for, 1969-1970; 12 binders (Box A-336)
  - Higher Education, Commission for, 1970; 5 binders (Box A-337)
  - Higher Education, Commission for, 1965-1967; 5 inches (Box A-337)
  - Higher Education, Commission for, 1963-1970; 12 inches (Box A-338)
  - Higher Education, Conn. Foundation for Financial Assistance to, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box A-339)
  - Higher Education, Federal Aid to, 1964-1967 (Box A-339)
  - Higher Education, New England Board of, 1961-1967 (Box A-339)
  - Highway Department, 1962-1968; 5 folders (Box A-339)
  - Highway Department, 1957, 1965-1969; 12 inches (Box A-340)
  - Highway Department, 1961-1963, 1967-1970; 11 inches (Box A-341)
  - Highway Department Investigation, 1964; 2 folders (Box A-341)
  - Highway Department Minutes, 1969; 1 binder (Box A-342)
  - Highway Department Organization Study (8 folders)[1957], 8 folders (Box A-342)
  - Housing Division - Public Works Department, 1961-1965, 1967; 4 folders (Box A-342)
  - Human Rights & Opportunities Commission, 1965-1970; 2 folders (Box A-342)
  - Human Rights Council, 1964 (Box A-342)
  - Hypertrichologists, Board of, 1964 (Box A-342)
  - Insurance Department, 1961-1965, 1966, 1969; 2 folders (Box A-342)
  - Intergovernmental Cooperation, Commission on, 1961-1966 (Box A-342)
  - Investment Committee, 1961-1966, 1968-1969 (Box A-343)
  - Jail Administrator (Harold E. Hegstrom), 1961-1968; 2 folders (Box A-343)
  - Judicial Department, 1961, 1963-1966 (Box A-343)
  - Juvenile Court, 1959-1961, 1964, 1969 (Box A-343)
  - Labor Department, 1966-1968 (Box A-343)
  - Labor Department, 1962-1970; 11 inches (Box A-344)
  - Labor Relations, Board of (Box A-344)
  - Laurel Heights Hospital - Shelton (Box A-345)
  - Legislative Council Files - George W. Oberst, Director, 2 folders (Box A-345)
  - Legislative Research Department (Box A-345)
  - Library, State, 3 folders (Box A-345)
  - Liquor Control Commission, 2 folders (Box A-345)
  - Long Lane School, 1961-1962, 1967, 1969 (Box A-346)
  - Mansfield State Training School, 1964 (Box A-346)
  - Mansfield State Training School, 1962-1963 (Box A-346)
  - Mansfield State Training School, 1955-1961 (Box A-346)
  - Medical Examining Board, 1958 (Box A-346)
  - Mental Health, 1963-1967 (Box A-346)
  - Mental Health Department, 1961-1963, 1965, 1967-1970; 3 folders (Box A-346)
  - Mental Health, Interstate Compact, 1955, 1957-1958, 1965 (Box A-346)
  - Mental Retardation, Office of, 1962-1965 (Box A-347)
  - Merit Award Board, Employees, 1963 (Box A-347)
  - Military, 1965, 1967-1970; 11 inches (Box A-347)
  - Military Department, 1967-1968 (Box A-347)
  - Military Department, 1956, 1959-1961, 1964 (Box A-348)
  - Motor Vehicles Department, 1961-1970 (Box A-348)
  - Motor Vehicles Department, 1962-1967; 8 inches (Box A-349)
  - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, 1963-1965 (Box A-349)
  - Naturopathic, Examiners, Board of, 1963 (Box A-349)
  - Norwich State Hospital, 1962-1963, 1970 (Box A-349)
  - Nursing, Board of Examiners for, 1969 (Box A-349)
  - Opticians, Commission, 1969 (Box A-349)
  - Osteopathic Examining Board, 1964 (Box A-349)
  - Park and Forest Commission, 1962-1966. 1969-1970 (Box A-349)
  - Park and Forest Commission, 1955-1970; 2 folders (Box A-350)
  - Personnel Appeal Board, 1969-1970 (Box A-350)
  - Personnel Department, 1961-1969 (Box A-350)
  - Physical Therapists, 1963 (Box A-350)
  - Podiatry, Board of Examiners, 1964 (Box A-350)
  - Prison Association, 1959-1970 (Box A-350)
  - Psychologists, Board of Examiners, 1963-1964 (Box A-350)
  - Public Utilities Commission, 1966-1970; 5 inches (Box A-350)
  - Public Utilities Commission, 1961-1962, 1964-1965 (Box A-351)
  - Public Works Department, 1965-1970; 10 inches (Box A-351)
  - Public Works Department, 1961-1962 (Box A-352)
  - Purchasing Division, 1956, 1959-1961, 1966 (Box A-352)
  - Recreation, undated (Box A-352)
  - Retirement, 1967-1970; 9 inches (Box A-352)
  - Retirement Commission, 1962-1970; 5 inches (Box A-353)
  - Retirement Commission, 1962-1970; 7 inches (Box A-353)
  - Retirement Commission, 1961-1963; 2 folders (Box A-354)
  - School for Boys, 1962, 1965-1967, 1970 (Box A-354)
  - Seaside Regional Center (Seaside Hospital), 1961-1962, 1967-1968 (Box A-354)
  - Secretary of State, 1957-1969 (Box A-354)
  - Shellfish Commission, 1969-1970 (Box A-354)
  - Soldiers, Sailors and Marines Fund, 1957, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1970 (Box A-354)
  - Southbury Training School, 1956-1958, 1961-1963, 1969 (Box A-354)
  - Spanish War Veterans, 1964-1965 (Box A-354)
  - State Editor, 1956 (Box A-354)
  - State Farm for Women, 1960-1962, 1964, 1966 (Box A-354)
  - State Police, 1960-1964, 1967; 3 folders (Box A-354)
  - State Police, 1961-1964, 1967; 9 inches (Box A-355)
  - State Prison, 1956-1963; 2 folders (Box A-355)
  - State Prison, 1961-1968; 4 inches (Box A-356)
  - State Prison Industries Advisory Committee, 1957-1959 (Box A-356)
  - State Prison - Riot Plan, 1957 (Box A-356)
  - State Prison, Wethersfield: Executive Order, P.A. 28 and P.A. 459 of 1963 G.A., 1963, 1967-1970 (Box A-356)
  - Steamship Terminals, Commission on, 1955, 1962-1969 (Box A-356)
  - Suggestion Award Board, State Employee, 1966 (Box A-356)
  - Tax Department, 1965-1970; 3 folders (Box A-356)
  - Tax Department, 1955, 1958-1964; 2 folders (Box A-357)
  - Teachers' Retirement Board, 1963-1964, 1967-1968 (Box A-357)
  - Traffic Commission, 1961-1965 (Box A-357)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1961-1967; 7 inches (Box A-357)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1965-1970; 12 inches (Box A-358)
  - Tree Protection Examining Board, 1963-1964 (Box A-359)
  - Tuberculosis and other Chronic Diseases, Committee on, 1958-1959 (Box A-359)
  - Tuberculosis Control, Hospital Care and Rehabilitation, 1961 (Box A-359)
  - Uncas-on-Thames, 1962, 1967, 1970 (Box A-359)
  - Undercliff, 1958, 1962 (Box A-359)
  - Unemployment Commission, 1963-1964 (Box A-359)
  - University of Conn. - published material, 1962-1964; 6 inches (Box A-359)
  - University of Conn. - published material, 1967-1969; 12 inches (Box A-360)
  - University of Conn. - published material, 1968-1970; 12 inches (Box A-361)
  - University of Conn. - published material, 1963-1967, 1970; 12 inches (Box A-362)
  - University of Conn. - published material, 1961-1966; 12 inches (Box A-363)
  - University of Conn., 1955-1956, 1958, 1960; 3 folders (Box A-364)
  - University of Conn. Branch Library, 1968 (Box A-364)
  - University of Conn. - Dental and Medical School, 1965-1967 (Box A-364)
  - University of Conn. - Health Center, 1965-1970 (Box A-364)
  - University of Conn. - Metallurgy and Materials Science, 1964 (Box A-364)
  - University of Conn. - Middlesex Branch, 1963-1965 (Box A-364)
  - University of Conn. - Southeastern Conn. Branch, 1963-1964 (Box A-364)
  - Veterans Home and Hospital, 1958, 1960-1963, 1966-1970; 4 inches (Box A-365)
  - Veterinary Board of Reg. & Examination, 1960 (Box A-365)
  - Water Resources Commission, 1961, 1967-1970; 7 inches (Box A-365)
  - Water Resources Commission, 1957-1959 (Box A-366)
  - Welfare, 1960-1967; 5 folders (Box A-366)
  - Welfare, Aid to Dependent Children, 1961 (Box A-366)
  - Welfare, Commission to Study Revision of Laws (2 folders), 1952-1953, 1955-1957, 1959-1966; 2 folders (Box A-366)
  - Welfare, Commissioner, 1969-1970 (Box A-366)
  - Welfare Dept., 1959-1963, 1967-1970; 12 inches (Box A-367)
  - Welfare Dept., 1959-1963, 1968-1970; 6 inches (Box A-368)
  - Welfare Dept., Family Rehabilitation Program, 1962 (Box A-368)
  - Welfare Dept., March on, 1966-1968 (Box A-368)
  - Welfare Dept., P.A. 730, 1969 (Box A-368)
  - Welfare Dept., Physicians' Fees, 1962-1969 (Box A-368)
  - Welfare Dept., Reclassification, 1964, 1966, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box A-369)
  - Welfare Dept., Rent Gouging, 1962 (Box A-369)
  - Welfare Dept., Reports to Governor, 1961-1969 (Box A-369)
  - Welfare Dept., Santos, Carmen, 1968 (Box A-369)
  - Welfare Dept., Study of Operations, 1959 (Box A-369)
  - Welfare Dept., Work Training Program, 1962, 1969 (Box A-369)
  - [Henry] Whitfield State Museum, 1959 (Box A-369)
  - Wholesale Milk Producers Council, 1961 (Box A-369)
  - Workmen's Compensation Commission, 1958-1962 (Box A-369)
- Series 5. Civil Defense Files, 1961-1970
  Plans, correspondence, publications, clippings, etc.
  Unarranged.
  No container listing.
  - Records (Box A-370 - A-374)
- Series 6. New Haven Rail Road and Connecticut Transportation Authority Files, 1955-1970
  Correspondence, reports, publications, clippings, largely pertaining to the N.H.R.R., its financial difficulties and merger with the Pennsylvania Rail Road, and related matters.
  Largely unarranged.
  - Records (Box A-375 - A-389)
- Series 7. Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1959-1968
  - Records (Box A-390 - A-395)
- Series 8. National Governors' Conference Files, 1958-1970
  - Democratic Governors' Meeting, Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri, 1970 August 11 (Box A-396)
  - National Democratic Governors' Financial (Box A-396)
  - Democratic Governors' Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1969 October 22 (Box A-396)
  - National Democratic Governors' Conference (Box A-396)
    - National Governors Mid-winter Conference, Washington, D.C., 1968 February 28-March 1 (Box A-396)
    - Social Security Amendments (Box A-396)
    - Constitutional Revision in General Government Organization (Box A-396)
    - Reservations - Receptions - White House Invitations (Box A-396)
    - Conference Material General (Box A-396)
    - Price, Daniel (Box A-396)
    - Civil Defense (Box A-396)
    - Banking Resolutions (Box A-396)
    - Footwear Exhibit Invitations (Box A-396)
    - Udall Letter (Box A-396)
    - Various Reports of the 1968 National Governors' Conference (Box A-396)
    - Various Reports of the 1968 National Governors' Conference, Part II (Box A-396)
  - National Governors' Conference Federal-State/Local Relations Committee, 1968 (Box A-396)
    - [List of Governors' and Addresses, List of Staff Assistants] (Box A-396)
  - National Governors' Conference Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box A-396)
  - National Governors' Conference Federal-State Committee Social Unrest & Violence (Box A-397)
  - National Governors' Conference, Washington, D.C., 1968 March 1 (Box A-397)
  - National Governors' Conference, Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri, 1970 August 9-12 (Box A-397)
    - Agenda Items (Box A-397)
    - Miscellaneous (Box A-397)
    - Committee on Rural and Urban Development (Box A-397)
  - National Governors' Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1968 July 22-24 (Box A-397)
    - Preliminary Correspondence (Box A-397)
    - Agenda (Box A-397)
    - Federal-State Relations (Box A-397)
    - Miscellaneous (Box A-397)
    - Gun Control Legislation (Box A-397)
    - Omnibus Crime Control Bill "Block Grant" Resolutions (Box A-397)
    - State Urban Relations Committee Report (Box A-397)
    - State Bank Investments (Box A-397)
    - Resolutions (Box A-397)
  - National Governors' Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1968 (Box A-398)